Guide to the ILGWU. General Executive Board minutes, 1913-1995.
ILGWU. General Executive Board minutes,
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ILGWU. General Executive Board minutes, 1913-1995.
5780/016
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. General Executive Board.
16 linear feet
Minutes, reports.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Includes the minutes and reports of the General Executive Board of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
ILGWU ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The International Ladies’ Garment Workers’ Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women’s garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the “new unionism,” the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers’ strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers’ strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the “protocol of peace,” a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes the minutes and reports of the General Executive Board of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
SUBJECTS
Names:
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. General Executive Board.
Subjects:
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.; Correspondence.; Microfilm reels.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
RELATED MATERIALS
5780. ILGWU Records
5780/016mf. ILGWU. General Executive Board minutes. Microfilm
5780/018. ILGWU. General Executive Board. Appeal Committee cases
5780/189. ILGWU. Perry Parker papers
NOTES
"Permanent deposit"
SERIES LIST
Series I. Executive Board Minutes, 1913-1973
Series II. Bound Executive Board Minutes, 1926-1957
Series III. Executive Board Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1970-1995
Series IV. Committee Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1948-1978
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Executive Board Minutes, 1913-1973
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1913-1917 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1913-1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1913-1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1917-1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1917-1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1917-1920 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1925-1928 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1925-1928 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1925-1928 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1942 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1942 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 4 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 5 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 6 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 7 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 3 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 4 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 5 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 6 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 7 of 7], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Series II. Bound Executive Board Minutes, 1926-1957
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1926-1928 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    bound copy
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1929-1932 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1949-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes. General., 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Series III. Executive Board Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1970-1995
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1974 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 6], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 6], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 6], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 6], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 6], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 6], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General., 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)